I find it deeply disturbing that so many folks say that you know people like Barack Obama who
have served in the presidency that they should retire and they should retire they should not
ever retire being for the people they never retire being for the Democrats they seem to
always have time to come and say something for the Democrats I mean do you get to retire
they're taking social security and yet you're arguing for the right of people who
have health care and protection and money for the rest of their lives guaranteed to not have to help
you after you elected them I don't the the fight doesn't retire you think Dr. Martin Luther King
would have ever retired if he wasn't assassinated Fannie Lou Hamer never retired Reverend Shelsworth
never retired John Lewis never retired you shift you change how you engage even your body your output is
not going to be the same but to think that it is no longer your problem it's just simply unrealistic
because on a basic level you should be working with teaching and consulting those who are coming up
to carry forward what you may not have the ability and capability to continue to do
so this idea that we retire as black folks because we're no longer elected officials
in our expectancy to speak to work with organizers to use the power that we still have as former heads
of state to advance efforts of elevation of equality of disruption is nonsense to me the fact that you
seem to think I'm only talking to the ones who seem to think this that because someone is no longer an
elected official they should no longer be expected to be a part of creating a world that is better
for all of us even though the ones who are still elected are actively creating a world that is
terrible for all of us says everything that everyone needs to know about why we're in this world that
we're in in the first place because the real truth is a lot of you mofos ain't gonna fight for yourself
so what's the plan
a man